大伙们 中央咖啡厅很荣幸为大家介绍
Everybody. Shh. Uh, Central Perk is proud to present...
菲比布非小姐的音乐
the music of Miss Phoebe Buflay.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨 我要为大家演唱一首歌 歌曲内容描述
Hi. Um, I wanna start with a song that's about that moment...
你突然间明白 人生真正意义的那一刹那
when you suddenly realize what life is really all about.
好吧 要开始了
Okay, here we go.
好 非常感谢大家
Okay. Thank you very much.
什么?
What?
太棒了 这真是...
Oh, great. This is just...
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第07集
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：阿汨
停电记
The One With the Blackout
这真的是太酷了 你们快看
This is so cool, you guys.
全市大停电
The entire city is blacked out.
妈妈说是整个曼哈顿
Mom says it's Manhattan,
布鲁克林以及皇后区都停电了
Brooklyn and Queens...
而且还不知道什么时候能来电
and doesn't know when it'll be back on.
大伙们 这是大消息
Wow. You guys, this is big.
长裤跟毛衣 怎么了? 妈
Pants and a sweater. Why, Mom?
停电的时候我还能遇见谁?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
电力公司的人? 单身强盗?
Power-company guys? Eligible looters?
我们能待会再谈这个吗? 好吧
Can we talk about this later? Okay.
我能借用一下电话吗?
Can I borrow the phone?
我想打回我家看看我奶奶是否还好
I wanna call my apartment and check on my grandma.
我家电话号码是多少?
What's my number?
我又没给自己打过电话
I never call me.
天啊 是她
Oh, my God. It's her.
那是维多利亚的秘密的模特儿
It's that Victoria Secret model.
她叫古德克什么来着的
Something Goodacre.
妈 我是吉儿
Hi Mom. It's Jill.
她说的对 她是吉儿 吉儿古德克
She's right. It's Jill. Jill Goodacre.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我跟吉儿古德克 被困在提款机的门廊里
l am trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
这是提款机的门廊吗? 或许是提款机的中庭才对
Is it a vestibule? Maybe it's an atrium?
对 那才是重点 白痴
Yeah，that is the part to focus on, you idiot.
我没事 我只是被困在提款机的门廊里
Yeah I'm fine. I'm just stuck at the bank in an ATM vestibule.
吉儿说这是门廊
Jill says vestibule...
我投门廊一票
I'm going with vestibule.
我没事
I'm fine.
我不是一个人
No，I'm not alone.
我不知道 一个男人
I don't know. Some guy.
哦 一个男人 一个男人
Oh, some guy. I am some guy.
吉儿 昨晚我看到你跟一个男人在一起
Hey, Jill，I saw you with some guy last night.
是啊 一个男人
Yes, he was some guy.
大家好
Hey, everyone.
主持今晚停电仪式的是 崔比亚尼祭司
Officiating at tonight's black out is Rabbi Tribbiani.
钱德的前任室友是犹太人 我们只有这种蜡烛
Chandler's old roommate was Jewish, and these are the only candles we have.
光明节快乐
so happy Hanukkah everyone.
你们看 裸体丑男点了一堆蜡烛
Ooh, look. Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
那一定很痛
Ooh. That had to hurt.
好吧 已经过了十四分钟半
All right, all right. It's been 14 and a half minutes...
你一句话都没说 天啊
...and you still haven't said one word. Oh God.
快做点什么 主动跟她接触 笑一个
Do something. Just make contact. Smile.
很不错
There you go.
你吓坏她了
You're definitely scaring her.
你要打电话吗?
Uh, would you like to call somebody?
是的 我要打给 三百位高中同学
Yeah, about 300 guys I went to high school with.
对 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
喂
Hello?
是我      是钱德 你没事吧?
It's me.        It's Chandler. Are you okay?
我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我被困在提款机的门廊
I'm stuck in an ATM vestibule...
跟吉儿古德克在一起
...with Jill Goodacre.
什么?
What?
我被困在
I'm stuck...
提款机的门廊
in an ATM vestibule...
跟吉儿古德克在一起
...with Jill Goodacre.
我完全听不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you said.
叫乔伊来听电话
Put Joey on the phone.
什么事?
What's up, man?
我被困在
I'm stuck...
提款机的门廊
in an ATM vestibule...
跟吉儿古德克在一起
...with Jill Goodacre.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他被困在提款机的门廊 跟吉儿古德克在一起
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
钱德 听着
Chandler, listen.
别以为我没那种念头
Yeah, like that thought never entered my mind.
快一点
Come on, somebody.
轮到我了
I'll go. I'll go.
大四那年在撞球台上
Okay, um, senior year of college, on a pool table.
撞球台?
Pool table?
这就是我妹妹
That's my sister.
我最奇怪的地点是...
Okay, okay. My weirdest place would have to be...
纽约市立图书馆二楼的女厕
...the women's room on the second floor of the New York City Public Library.
天啊 你去图书馆做什么?
Oh, my God. What were you doing in a library?
菲比 你呢?      密尔瓦基
Pheebs, what about you?        Oh, um, Milwaukee.
罗斯
Uh. Ross?
一九八九年 迪士尼乐园的小小世界
Disneyland 1989. "It's a small world after all."
不可能
No way.
游乐设施坏了
The, uh, ride broke down...
卡萝跟我躲在那些荷兰机器儿童后面
Carol and I went behind a couple of those mechanical Dutch children.
他们修好游乐施备后 要我们永远别回魔法王国
Then they fixed the ride, and we were asked never to return to the Magic Kingdom.
瑞秋      少来 我已经说过了
Ooh. Rachel?        I already went.
才没有      我说过了
You did not go.        Yes, I did.
快告诉我们
Tell us. Come on.
好吧 我最奇怪的地点是...
All right, uh, the weirdest place would have to be...
床脚
...the foot of the bed.
不会吧?      冠军已经出炉
Step back.        We have a winner.
我从没有过那么激情的关系
I've never had a relationship with that kind of passion.
一定要在游乐园跟某人做爱
Where you have to have somebody right there in the middle of a theme park.
那是那里唯一不必排队的地方
It was the only thing to do there that didn'thave a line.
巴里连在迷你高尔夫球场 都不愿意吻我
Well, Barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature-golf course.
真的假的      真的
Come on.        No.
他说我们会挡到后面的人
He said we were holding up the people behind us.
你没有嫁给他是因为...
And you didn't marry him because...?
你觉得有人终其一生
Do you think there are people that go through life...
都没有干过那种事情...
never having that kind of...
或许吧      真的吗?
Probably.        Really?
但我得告诉你一件事 大家都太高估激情了
I'll tell you something. Passion is way overrated.
对      没错
Yeah, right.        It is.
最终激情会褪去
Eventually, it kind of burns out.
但是好在留下了信任和安全感以及...
But hopefully what you're left with is trust and security and, uh....
以我前妻为例吧 成了女同志
In my exwife's case, lesbianism.
对那些错过激情的人来说
For all those people who miss out on that, uh, passion thing...
还是能得到一些好处的
there's other good stuff.
好吧
Okay.
我不相信那种事会发生在你身上
But, um, I don't think that'll be you.
是吗?
You don't?
我看得出来 未来你会有段充满激情的感情
See, I see, uh... big passion in your future.
真的吗?
Really?
你那么认为?      没错
You do?        I do.
罗斯 你真的是太棒了
Ross, you're so great.
那是不可能的
It's never gonna happen.
什么?      你跟瑞秋
What?        You and Rachel.
为什么?
Why not?
因为你迟迟不肯展开行动
Because you waited too long to make your move...
现在你们进入"朋友区"
and now you're in the "Friend Zone."
不 我不在那一区
No, no, no. I'm not in the Zone.
罗斯 你甚至是区长呢
No Ross. You're mayor of the Zone.
我只是在慢慢来 好吗?
Look, I'm taking my time, all right?
我在打基础
I'm　laying the groundwork.
对 每天我越来越靠近...
Every day I get a little bit closer to, uh...
成为神父的日子
Priesthood.
罗斯 我得告诉你 她根本不知道你在想什么
Ross, I'm telling you, she has no idea what you're thinking.
如果你不赶快约她出去 你们会永远只能做朋友
If you don't ask her out soon，you'll end up stuck in the Zone forever.
我会的 我只是...
I will, I will.
在等时机成熟
I'm waiting for the, uh, right moment.
什么?
What?
现在?      对
What, now        Yeah.
你觉得哪里不对劲?美酒?
What's messing you up? The wine?
蜡烛?月光?
The candles? The moonlight? Huh?
你只需要走过去跟她说 "瑞秋 我…"
You gotta go up to her and say, "Look, Rachel, I think"
什么?      我们会嘘个不停
What are we shushing?        We're shushing...
是因为我们想听一些东西
because were trying to hear something.
什么声音?      你没听到吗?
What?        Uh, dont you hear that?
听到了?
See?
你要吃口香糖吗?      是无糖的吗?
Would you like some gum?        Oh. Is it sugarless?
抱歉 不是      不用了 谢谢
Uh, sorry, it's not.        Then, no, thanks.
那是怎么一回事?
What the hell was that?
别忘了 如果吉儿古德克请你吃口香糖 一定要接受
Mental Note: If Jill Goodacre offers you gum, you take it.
就算她要你吃动物尸体 你也得接受
If she offers you mangled animal carcass, you take it.
纽约市停电了
New York City has no power
牛奶发臭了
And the milk is getting sour
但我一点都不怕
But to me it is not scary
因为我不吃奶
'Cause I stay away from dairy
来吧      你要开口了?
Here goes.        You'll do it?
没错      需要我帮忙吗?
I'll do it.        Want help?
你敢出来就死定了
You come out there, you're a dead man.
罗斯
Ross, Ross.
祝你好运
Good luck, man.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧      好吧
Okay.        Okay.
你要去哪里?      外面
Where you going?        Outside.
你不能出去
You can't go out there.
为什么?      那是有原因的
Why not?        Because of, uh, the reason.
什么原因?
And that would be?
我不能告诉你      乔伊 发生了什么事?
I, uh I can't tell you.        What's going on?
听着 你得发誓 你不会告诉罗斯是我说的
Okay, listen. You gotta promise you'll never, ever tell Ross that I told you.
什么事?      他在筹划你的生日派对
About what?        He's planning your birthday party.
天啊 我爱他
Oh, my God. I love him.
你最好表现出讶异的样子
You better act surprised.
为什么?      我的惊喜派对
About what?        My surprise party.
什么惊喜派对?      别装了 乔伊都跟我说了
What surprise party?        Oh, stop it. Joey already told me.
他没有告诉我
Well, he didn'ttell me.
别看我 那是罗斯的事
Don't look at me. This is Ross'thing.
这太老套了 每次我都是最后知道的人
This is so typical. I'm always the last to know everything.
才怪 我们告诉你很多事
You are not. We tell you stuff.
钱德在动物园被孔雀咬伤 我是最后一个知道的人
I was the last one to know when Chandler got bit by the peacock at the zoo.
我是最后一个知道
I was the last to know
当乔伊刚搬进来时你对他有意思
you had a crush on Joey when he was moving in.
什么?
What?
看起来我是倒数第二个
Oh. Looks like I was second to last.
真的好漂亮
It's so nice.
我有个问题
Hey, I have a question.
事实上它算不上是个问题
Uh, actually, it's not so much a question...
那只是好奇...
it's more of a general wondering...
而已
...ment.
好吧      好吧
Okay.        Okay.
我要说了
Here goes.
我一直都想要...
Um, well for a while now, I've been wanting to, um...
噢      没错
Oh.        Yes, that's right.
看看那只小猫味
Look at that little kitty.
什么?
What?
我攀上世界顶端 俯瞰众生
I'm on the top of the world Looking down on creation
我能找到的唯一解释
And the only explanation I can find
就是自从你出现我才找到的真爱
Is the love that I found Ever since you ye been around
好吧 这是急救喷雾剂 不会痛的
All right, this is just Bactine. It won't hurt.
抱歉 那是蜡
Sorry, that was wax.
可怜的小托蒂吓得半死 我们得找到他的主人
Poor little Tootie's scared. We should find his owner.
我们何不将可怜小托蒂放在走廊上?
Why not put "poor little Tootie" in the hall?
在停电的时候? 它会绊倒的
During a blackout? She'll get trampled.
是吗?
Yeah?
我想了一下 口香糖很完美
You know, on second thought, gum would be perfection.
口香糖很完美?
Gum would be perfection?
口香糖很完美
Gum would be perfection.
我应该说"口香糖很棒" 或"我要来一块" 但是不
Could've said, "Gum would be nice." "I'll have a stick." But, no.
对我来说口香糖很完美
For me, gum is perfection.
我恨自己
I loathe myself.
不 她们是修女 她们憎恨所有生物
Oh, no, the Mellons. They hate all living things, right?
嗨 我们刚刚发现这只猫 我们在找他的主人
Hi. We just found this cat...and we're looking for the owner
对 他是我的猫
Um, yeah, it's...uh...It's mine.
他似乎很讨厌你 你确定?
He seems to hate you. Are you sure?
对 他是我的猫 快还我
Yeah. It's my cat. Give me my cat.
等一下 他叫什么名字?
Wait a minute. What's his name?
巴伯...钮扣
Um, Bob...Buttons.
巴伯钮扣?
Bob Buttons?
没错 来吧 巴伯钮扣
Bob Buttons. Here, Bob Buttons.
你是个大坏蛋
You are a very bad man.
你们欠我一只猫
You owe me a cat.
来吧 小猫味
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty.
你跑到哪里去了? 小猫咪
Where did you go, little kitty, kitty, kitty?
小猫味 快来吧...
Kitty, kitty, kitty. Come here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty...
嗨
Hi.
来吧 幸运数字六
Come on, lucky sixes.
大伙们 他是巴洛
Everybody, this is Paolo.
巴洛 我来跟你介绍我的朋友
Paolo, I want you to meet my friends.
她是莫妮卡      嗨
This is Monica...        Hi.
乔伊      嗨
...and Joey.        Hi.
罗斯      嗨
...and Ross.        Hi.
他不太会说英文
Ha, ha. He doesn't speak much English.
大富翁
Monopoly.
快看
Look at that.
那么...
So, uh...
巴洛是哪来的?
Where did, uh, Paolo come from?
我想是意大利
Italy, I think. Heh.
不 我是说今晚他是从哪里 突然进入我们的生活里
No, I mean tonight, in the building? Suddenly into our lives？
那只猫是巴洛的猫 真的很有趣吧?
The cat turned out to be Paclo's cat. Isn't that funny?
那真的很有趣 瑞秋一直摸他
That is funny. And Rachel keeps touching him.
我到处找过了 但就是找不到那只猫
I looked all over the building and I couldn't find the kitty anywhere.
我找到他了 他是巴洛的猫
Oh, I found him. It was Paolo's cat.
又来了 我又是最后一个知道的人
Ah. Well, there you go. Last to know again.
既然没有人告诉我 我想他是巴洛吧?
And I'm guessing, since nobody told me, this is Paolo?
巴洛 她是菲比
Oh. Paolo, this is Phoebe.
说得对
You betcha.
好吧 接下来是什么?
All right. Okay. What next?
吹泡泡 好主意
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
那是种稚气的魅力 看起来很顽皮
It's got a, uh, boyish charm. It's impish.
来吧
Here we go.
做得好 小顽皮
Nice going, imp.
没事 我只需要...
Okay. It's okay. All I need to do is...
伸手将它塞回嘴里
...reach over and put it back in my mouth.
救得好 回到正轨 我...
Good save. We're back on track and I'm...
在吃别人的口香糖
...chewing someone else's gum.
这不是我的口香糖 天啊
This is not my gum. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
你现在噎住了
And now you're choking.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
天啊 你噎住了
Oh, my God. You're choking.
好一点了吗?
Better?
对 谢谢 那是...
Yes. Thank you. That was...
那是...
That was...
完美?
Perfection?
他说了什么事那么好笑?
What'd he say that was so funny?
我真的不知道
I have absolutely no idea.
那太老套了
That's classic.
天啊 大伙们 我在做什么?
My God, you guys. What am I doing?
这太不像我了
This is so un-me.
如果你答应 我可以帮你上
If you want, I'll do it.
我知道 我好想咬住他的下唇
I know. I just wanna bite his bottom lip.
但我不会那么做
But I won't.
天啊 他第一次对着我笑时
God. The first time he smiled at me...
那三秒钟比我跟巴里 在百慕达度过的三星期刺激
those three seconds were more exciting than three weeks in Bermuda with Barry.
你们有租摩托车吗?
Did you rent mopeds?
因为我听说...
Because I've heard...
那不是现在的重点
Oh, it's not about that right now. Okay.
我知道这超肤浅 而且我们没有任何共通点
I know it's totally superficial, and we have nothing in common...
连说的语言都不一样
...and we don'teven speak the same language...
但是天啊
...but, God.
巴洛 嗨
Paolo, hi.
罗斯      听着
Ross.        Listen. uh...
听着 有件事你必须知道
Listen, um, heh, something you should, uh, know.
瑞秋跟我...
Rachel and I are...
我们之间有感觉
We're kind of a thing.
感觉?      对 感觉
Thing?        Thing. Yes, thing.
你们有性关系?      不
You have the sex?        No.
不 技术上来说我们没有性关系 但那…
No, no. Um, technically, the sex is not being had. But that's, uh...
那不是重点
That's not the point.
重点是瑞秋跟我应该...
The point is that, uh, Rachel and I should be. uh...
瑞秋跟我应该在一起
Well Rachel and I should be together.
如果你...
And if you get in the, uh...
上床?      不
In bed?        No.
不 我不是那个意思
Ha. No, not where I was going.
如果你介入我们之间
If you get in the way of us becoming a thing...
那么我会非常难过
then, uh, I would be, well, very sad.
所以你...
So do you, um...?
你会的英文不多?      我只懂一些
You do know a little English?        Little.
你知道什么是"讨厌鬼"吗?
Do you know the word crapweasel?
不 那真的很有趣 你是讨厌鬼
No? That's funny, you are a huge crapweasel.
钱德 我们已经玩了一小时 看好了 真的很简单
Chandler, we've been here for an hour doing this. Watch, it'seasy.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
好吗? 试试看
Okay? Now try it.
不 你得把它甩出去
You gotta whip it.
快看 最后一根蜡烛要熄了
Look, look. The last candle's about to burn out.
十 九 八 七...
Ten， nine, eight, seven...
负46 负47 负48...
minus 46, minus 47, minus 48...
谢谢      谢谢
Thank you.        Thanks.
没有灯光感觉好恐怖
Kind of spooky without any lights.
大伙们 我有个好点子
Okay, guys, I have the definitive one.
罗斯 或许我不该在这个时候说
Uh, Ross...This probably isn't the best time to bring it up...
但你得帮莫妮卡办个派对
but you have to throw a party for Monica.
这真的太好玩了      对
This has been fun.        Yes.
谢谢你借我电话
Yes. Thanks for uh, letting me use your phone...
还救了我一命
and for saving my life.
再见 钱德
Well, goodbye, Chandler.
停电时我玩得很开心
I had a great blackout.
再见
See you.
我的帐号是7143457 我不知道你们有没有拍到
Hi. Um I'm account number 7143457. And I don't know if you got any of that...
但我真的很想要拷贝一卷录影带
...but I would really like a copy of the tape.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧